titusmedia.com 2010-12-31

# Publishers - Titus Media - Your Power Through Media

Titus Media, Inc. (TM) is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains the type of information TM collects through its website and what TM does with it. Please read the following privacy policy carefully before using the TM website. If you use the TM website, you will be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. This policy may change from time to time so you should check it frequently. TM does not attempt to determine the identity of any TM user by analyzing Web usage paths. 

If you are visiting titusmedia.com and you search the internet from the website, we collect the following information: your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, which may include a domain name; the name of and information about any advertisement that brought you to the TM website; searches you perform, links you click on; and computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform. We also transmit cookies to your computer so we can know your browser's language, the version of our site you viewed and the country you are from. 

TM analyzes its logs of usage path collected from users to determine Web usage and shopping patterns of users in the aggregate. 

If you e-mail TM, we may store copies of such e-mail or similar communications between you and TM. This can result in the collection of your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information you may have in your e-mail text, addresses, or other fields, as well as the collection of the your IP address, the Internet or other routing of your communication, and the date and time of your communication. We do not attempt to correlate this information to your TM cookie number or your usage and shopping paths unless responding to your inquiry requires us to do so. 

Although these information logs may contain personally identifiable information, TM does not attempt to correlate cookie numbers, usage paths, or demographic information to your e-mail address and does not attempt to determine the identity of any TM user by analyzing this information, except as required by subpoenas, court orders or legal requirements. 

All transmissions between you and TM, including e-mails, URLs, cookie identification numbers, usage paths, and any personally identifiable information they might contain, pass through many third party machines, operating systems, programs, browsers, Web servers, networks, routers, Ethernet switches, ISPs, proxy servers, intranets, the public telephone systems, or other devices, any of which may create activity logs containing such transmissions. 

If you gave us your e-mail address, TM may contact you by e-mail to respond to reviews, ratings, and customer service inquiries you submit. We do not disclose your e-mail address to business partners or to anyone other than employees and agents working for or on behalf of TM, except as required by subpoenas, court orders, or legal requirements. We do not use your e-mail address to correlate your identity to your Web usage paths. 

How does TM share the information it collects? TM does not attempt to determine the identity of its users or correlate their e-mail addresses with their Web usage paths. Except as described below, TE does not intentionally disclose personally identifying information collected from any user to any third party without the user's consent. 

We do not use your cookies or usage paths to attempt to determine your identity. We use IP addresses to diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our website. Your IP address also is used by TM to gather broad demographic information, such as your general geographic location and Internet Service Provider. IP addresses are further used to help determine the number of TM users. This demographic information may also be used by TM to analyze aggregate Web usage behavior. 

We disclose any information we possess in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal requirements, and such information might be used by the receiving party to determine your identity, your Web usage or other things about you. We generally do not inform users of such requests for information, although we might try to do so in some cases. 

TM does not attempt to determine the identity of its users or correlate their e-mail addresses with their Web usage paths. Except as described below, TE does not intentionally disclose personally identifying information collected from any user to any third party without the user's consent. 

We provide "stripped" usage path information, demographic information, and shopping path information, to researchers, and other third parties. They use it to prepare analyses of aggregate Web patterns and trends. Such analyses are used in research and commercial reports. 

We disclose any information we possess in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal requirements, and such information might be used by the receiving party to determine your identity, your Web usage or other things about you. We generally do not inform users of such requests for information, although we might try to do so in some cases. 

All transmissions between you and TM, including e-mails, URLs, cookie identification numbers, usage paths, and any personally identifiable information they might contain, pass through many third party machines, operating systems, programs, browsers, Web servers, networks, routers, Ethernet switches, ISPs, proxy servers, intranets, the public telephone systems, or other devices, any of which may create activity logs containing such transmissions. 

If you gave us your e-mail address, TM may contact you by e-mail to respond to reviews, ratings, and customer service inquiries you submit. We do not disclose your e-mail address to business partners or to anyone other than employees and agents working for or on behalf of TM, except as required by subpoenas, court orders, or legal requirements. We do not use your e-mail address to correlate your identity to your Web usage paths. 

We do not use your cookies or usage paths to attempt to determine your identity. We use IP addresses to diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our website. Your IP address also is used by TM to gather broad demographic information, such as your general geographic location and Internet Service Provider. IP addresses are further used to help determine the number of TM users. This demographic information may also be used by TM to analyze aggregate Web usage behavior. 

TM does not attempt to determine the identity of its users or correlate their e-mail addresses with their Web usage paths. Except as described below, TM does not intentionally disclose personally identifying information collected from any user to any third party without the user's consent. 

We provide "stripped" usage path information, demographic information, and shopping path information, to researchers, and other third parties. They use it to prepare analyses of aggregate Web patterns and trends. Such analyses are used in research and commercial reports. 

We disclose any information we possess in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal requirements, and such information might be used by the receiving party to determine your identity, your Web usage or other things about you. We generally do not inform users of such requests for information, although we might try to do so in some cases. 

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf, such as technical support services. To perform those functions, it may be necessary for them to obtain access to TM 's databases and servers, which may contain personally identifying information about users. They may not use such access or information for any purpose other than that for which they are retained. 

In the event that TM or substantially all of its assets are sold or acquired, all information collected by TM would be transferred to the acquiring party. In any such transfer, however, such information would remain subject to any applicable terms and conditions, including the terms of this Privacy Policy and any amendment thereto. 

TM uses commercially reasonable computer security safeguards to protect its databases and servers against risks of loss, unauthorized access, destruction, misuse, modification, or inadvertent or improper disclosure of data. These risks, however, cannot be completely eliminated and TE therefore cannot guarantee complete security. TM prohibits its employees from using any of this information to determine your identity. 

No confidentiality for customer feedback. 

Feedback and other comments and statements that you chose to submit to TM by any means whether by e-mail to TM Customer Support, telephone, letter, or any other means shall be considered non confidential. TM is free to use such information on an unrestricted basis. Data collection and use practices by other businesses that are not controlled by TM. 

The TM website provides links to various features, services, and Web pages provided solely by our business partners or other organizations. The links take you to pages provided solely by those entities, although sometimes the pages are co-branded with the TM logo. You will be able to tell when another entity is involved with providing features, services, or Web pages, and any information about your interaction with those Web pages, including which pages and advertisements you view and any search terms or other information you enter, will be received by that other business. 

When you click on links to other businesses, those businesses may attach a cookie to your hard drive and may collect information about you. TM makes no claims or representations about what those businesses do or do not collect about you. Please review any terms of use and privacy policies of those other businesses to learn about their data collection and data use practices. 

Further, our business partners may post advertisements on pages co-branded with the TM logo. Those advertisements are transmitted to your browser directly by the advertiser or the business partner, not by TM, and those advertisers may transmit a cookie to your hard drive and may collect information about you. If an advertiser or its ad server has previously placed a cookie on your machine, it may recognize the cookie and learn you have visited our co-branded Web page or used our website even though you do not click on the advertisement. TM makes no claim or representations concerning what such advertisers do or do not collect about you, and refers you to those entities for information about their privacy practices. 

You acknowledge and agree that TM is not responsible for any content, advertising, products, or other materials on the websites (whether co-branded with the TM logo or not) of or available from other businesses that we do not control. You further acknowledge that TM shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on or through any such site or resource. 

TM does not collect any personally identifiable information or try to aggregate the different data we might have to identify an individual, you don't have to worry about changing the information that we gathered on your usage of our website. If you have more questions regarding the information that we collect or the way that we use it, do not hesitate to contact us. 

Titus Media Management Team
